{
    "quizData": [
        { "question": "Вопрос 1?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 1 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 2?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 2 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 3?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 3 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 4?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 4 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 5?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 1 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 6?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 2 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 7?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 3 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 8?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 4 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 9?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 1 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 10?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 2 }
    ],
    "rateQuizData": [
        { "question": "Вопрос 11?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 3 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 12?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 4 },
        { "question": "Вопрос 13?", "answers": ["Да", "Нет", "Естественно", "Никак нет"], "correct": 1 }
    ]
}